<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">QuestionsJava</string>

    <!--  front activity start-->
    <string name="front_btn_question">الاسئلة</string>
    <string name="front_btn_rate">تقييم التطبيق</string>
    <string name="second_answer_text">انقر علي الزر لعرض الاجابه</string>

    <!--  front activity end-->
    <string-array name="questions">

        <item> How does app data differ from user data?</item>
        <item>How should I store user credentials?</item>
        <item> What happens to roaming app data when an app is uninstalled?</item>
        <item>What happens to app data when an app is updated?</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--  answers  -->
    <string-array name="answers">

    <item>App data is state that an app manages within its app data folders (Local, Roaming, and Temporary, along with LocalCache on Windows Phone 8.1). Its existence is tied to the existence of the app so that uninstalling the app deletes the app data from that device. Roaming app data persists in the cloud independently (see the next question), and is shared between Windows and Windows Phone apps that have the same Package Family Name in their manifests. User data, like pictures, videos, music, and documents, is stored anywhere else on the file system or the cloud, in libraries or in other locations selected through the file picker or folder picker UI.
        The lifetime of user data is not tied to any particular app and is controlled entirely by the user </item>
        <item> Always store user credentials (user name and password), as well as similarly sensitive data, in the Credential Locker by using the Windows.Security.PasswordVault class. The contents of the locker are automatically encrypted and, by default, roam across the user’s devices (if allowed through PC Settings > OneDrive > Sync Settings > Other Settings > Passwords and the device is trusted). Locker contents are also isolated between apps. Note that although PasswordVault is designed around user names and passwords, you can use it to help secure other values such as API access keys or tokens; just assign a suitable user ID to the user name and assign the key/token to the password. In short, think of the Credential
    Locker as the security-oriented extension to the other elements of the app data API.</item>

        <item>As noted in the previous question, an app’s app data folders are removed from a device when the app is uninstalled. Roaming app data, however, persists in the cloud so long as the user has the same app installed on other devices. When the user uninstalls the app from all of his or her devices, roaming app data continues to persist in the cloud for a reasonable time (a matter of a few weeks) so that it’s still available if the user decides to reinstall the app within that time. Note that when you make a change to an app project in Microsoft Visual Studio and that
        change (such as changing the manifest) forces a full reinstall, app data is removed as part of the process.</item>
        <item>App data is preserved across app updates delivered by the Windows Store and the Windows Phone Store.
    So app updates must be prepared to load app data that was generated by any previous version of the app.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>